Hi!
嘿
- Hey! - Hi!
-嘿  -嘿
- How was the honeymoon? - Oh, incredible!
-蜜月过得怎么样  -哦  好极了
Champagne, candle-lit dinners,
香槟  烛光晚餐
moonlight walks on the beach.
还有银色沙滩漫步
It was so romantic.
非常浪漫
- Where's Mike? - He's at the doctor.
-那  迈克在哪呢   -哦  看病去了
He didn't poop while we were there.
我们在那的时候他都没拉粑粑
I'm glad you're back. I need your help.
很高兴你回来了  我正要你帮忙呢
Oh, why, what's up?
怎么啦  什么事儿
I have an audition for this play,
我有个试镜
and I have to speak French...
剧本要求有些台词说法语
...which, according to my resume,
而我的简历里说
I'm fluent in.
我法语很流利
Joey, you shouldn't lie on your resume.
乔伊   你不应该在简历里撒谎
Yeah, you really shouldn't.
对呀  你真的不应该
By the way,
哦  对了
how was that yearlong dig in Cairo?
你在开罗那一年的考古挖掘怎么样啊
It was okay.
还行啦
I did not know you spoke French.
我怎么不知道你会说法语
You're so sexy.
你真性感
Well, so will you help me?
那你愿意帮我吗
I really wanna be in this play.
我真的很想演这部戏
Sure.
当然
Seriously, stop it.
说真的  别再说法语了
I'm gonna jump on you.
不然我就扑到你身上去了
《老友记》第十季第十三集 乔伊说法语
《老友记》  第十季  第13集  乔伊说法语
- Hey. - Hi.
-嘿 -嗨
Why are you wearing my apron?
你干吗穿着我的围裙
I'm making cookies for Erica.
我在给艾瑞卡做饼干
We have to leave soon.
哦  对了  我们得快点儿去机场
Her plane comes in in about an hour.
她的飞机一小时后降落
When she gets here,
那她到了以后
is it okay if I introduce you two as my wife...
我能不能把你们俩介绍成我老婆
...and the woman who's carrying my child?
和我孩子她妈
No?
不行
Divorce?
你要离婚
- Hey. - Hey.
-嘿  -嘿
You know where Rachel is?
你们知道瑞秋在哪吗
No, we haven't haven't seen her since morning.
不知道  从今天早上就没见着她
It's unbelievable.
难以置信
She was supposed to meet me
她半小时前就该
a half-hour ago with Emma.
带着艾玛跟我碰头的
- Hey! - Hey!
-嘿  -嘿
These are for Erica!
这些是给艾瑞卡准备的
She's gonna eat all those cookies?
那她也吃不了这么多吧
Well, I want the baby to come out
我想让小宝宝生出来
all cute and fat!
可爱胖胖的
So why is Erica coming to visit?
艾瑞卡干吗要来这儿
We wanna get to know her better.
我们想跟她再熟悉熟悉  还有...
And she's never been to New York,
她没来过纽约
so she wants to see the tourist spots:
所以她想逛逛那些旅游景点
Statue of Liberty, Empire State Building.
自由女神像啦  帝国大厦啦
Oh, those places! There's always so many people,
那些滥地方  人总是挤的满满当当
and they're being corralled like cattle.
跟牛群被关进栅栏似的
And, you know, there's always some idiot who goes, "Moo."
还有  那儿总是有些傻瓜学牛叫
Well, if it annoys you so much,
要是那这么惹你烦
then why do you do it?
你干吗也那么做呢
Oh, hi. Hi. Thanks for showing up
哦  嗨  谢天谢地
30 minutes late.
你才晚了30分钟
Ross.
罗斯
No, I'm sure you have a great excuse.
不用多费口舌  我肯定你有个好借口
What was it, a hair appointment?
是什么  美发预约
A mani-pedi?
美甲
Barneys:纽约时尚精品店
还是巴尼斯大降价
My father had a heart attack.
我爸爸得了心脏病
While I was at Barneys.
在我逛巴尼斯的时候
- Oh, my God, Rach. - Honey?
-我的天啊  瑞秋  -亲爱的
- I'm so sorry. - Is he okay?
-我很抱歉  -他还好吧
Yeah, he's gonna be fine,
是的  他们说他会好的
but he's heavily sedated.
但还是打了很多镇静剂
Okay, I'm gonna go to Long lsland with you.
好吧  我跟你一起去长岛
I mean, you can't be alone right now.
你现在一个人怎么行
No, come on, I'm totally okay.
不用了  我还行
I don't need you to come.
我用不着你来
I can totally handle this on my own.
我一个人能行
Still, still, let me come for me.
尽管如此  还是让我来吧… 就算是为了我
Okay. If you really need to.
好吧  如果你真的需要的话
I bet someone could use
我看吃点莫妮卡刚烤好的饼干
one of Monica's freshly baked cookies.
你感觉会好点
Oh, I really could.
哦  我还真想吃点
All right, it seems pretty simple.
好的  这看起来很简单
Your first line is, "My name is Claude."
你的第一句台词是 "我的名字叫克劳德"
So just repeat after me.
好  跟我念
- Well, let's try it again. - Okay.
-呃  我们再试一遍  -好
It's not...
你跟我说的
...quite what I'm saying.
不太一样
Really? Sounds exactly the same to me.
真的  我听着一模一样啊
- It does, really? - Yeah.
-是吗  真的  -好吧
- Let's just try it again. - Okay.
-我们再试一遍  -好吧
- Really listen. - Got it.
-仔细听着  -好嘞
- Hey, you guys! - Hi.
-嘿  伙计们   -嘿
I want you to meet someone really special.
给你们介绍一个很特别的贵宾
Phoebe, this is Erica. And this is the baby!
菲比  这是艾瑞卡  这是小宝宝
- Joey, Erica, baby. - Hi.
-乔伊  艾瑞卡  宝宝   -嘿
Everyone, Erica! Baby!
大家伙儿  艾瑞卡  宝宝
Monica. Calm. Self.
莫妮卡  冷静...点儿
- Hey, sit down. - Thank you.
-请坐  -谢谢
It's really nice to meet you guys.
真高兴见到你们
I can't believe I'm here.
我都不敢相信来到这儿了
Well, welcome to New York City, or should I say:
欢迎来到纽约  或者我应该说
不知所云的法语
不知所云的法语
Why would you say that?
你干吗要说那个
Okay. What are you gonna be doing today?
你们今天打算干什么
Well, I wanna see everything!
哦  我想看看所有的地方
Times Square, Coney lsland, Rockefeller Center.
时代广场  科尼岛  洛克菲勒中心
Oh, you know what you should do?
哦  你知道你该干什么吗
You should walk to
你应该一路爬到
the top of the Statue of Liberty.
自由女神像的顶上
- Oh, yeah, let's do that. - Great.
-哦  对呀  我们去爬吧   -太好了
This baby better be really good.
这个小宝宝得够结实才行
Hi. Excuse me,
嗨  打扰一下
I'm here to see my father.
我来看望我的父亲
My name is Rachel Green.
我叫瑞秋·格林
And I'm Dr. Ross Geller.
我是罗斯·盖勒博士
Ross, please, this is a hospital.
罗斯  行了吧  这里是医院
Doctor:医生也是博士的意思
这词儿在这儿是有其他意义的
- So can we please go in? - Absolutely.
-那么  我们能进去吗   -当然
Rach, I think I'm gonna wait out here...
瑞秋  我想我还是等在外面吧
...because my throat is feeling a little scratchy.
我的喉咙有点痒
I don't wanna infect him.
我不想传染给他
Ross, please. Don't be so scared of him.
罗斯  得了  别那么怕他
I am not scared of him. I'm really sick.
我不是怕他  我真的病了
He's under sedation,
镇静剂药效还没退
so he's pretty much out.
所以他还在昏睡着
I'm feeling better.
我感觉好多了
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
That ear and nose hair trimmer I got him
我给他买的耳毛和鼻毛剪
was just money down the drain, huh?
算是白花钱了
Ms. Green?
格林小姐
Your father's doctor's on the phone
你爸爸的医生在电话上
if you'd like to speak to him.
你要不要跟他谈谈
Oh, great. Are you gonna be okay?
哦  好的  呃  你在这等着没事吧
He's unconscious. We'll be just fine.
他还不省人事  我想我们没事儿
Okay.
好
- Did the TV wake you? - No.
-是不是电视吧你吵醒了   -不是
When you put your feet up on my bed,
你把脚翘到我床上
you tugged on my catheter.
压住我的导尿管了
What are you doing here, Geller?
你来这儿干吗
Well, I came with Rachel,
我和瑞秋一块儿来的
who should be back any second.
她一会儿就回来
So, what's new?
最近怎么样
Oh, I had a little heart attack.
哦  我得了点儿心脏病
Right. Is it painful?
是吧  疼吗
What, the heart attack
什么  你是指心脏病
or sitting here talking to you?
还是指在这跟你聊天
Let's see if we can get that Rachel back in here.
看看能不能把瑞秋叫过来
So, what's new with you?
那你最近怎么样
Knocked up any more of my daughters lately?
是不是又让我别的女儿也怀孕了
Nope. Just the one. Rach!
没有  只有那一个  瑞秋
No!
不对
Okay, maybe if we just break it down.
好吧  也许我们应该拆散了试试
Okay, let's try it one syllable at a time.
好吧  我们试试一次一个音节
Okay, so repeat after me.
好的  跟我念
Great! Okay, faster.
很好  快一点
Okay, it's too hard. I can't teach you.
好吧  这太难了  我教不了你
What are you doing?
你干吗
I have to go
我得走了
before I put your head through a wall.
不然我要拿你的头撞墙了
Don't go, I need you!
不  别走  我需要你
My audition is tomorrow!
我明天就要试镜了
Hey. I was gonna make us some dinner...
嘿  我本来想做晚饭的
...but all I found in your dad's fridge
但是你爸的冰箱里
was bacon and heavy cream.
只有培根和奶油
I think we solved
我想我们找到
the mystery of the heart attack.
他得心脏病的原因了
Did you call your parents?
你给你父母打电话了吗
Oh, yeah. Emma's doing great.
哦  打过了  艾玛很好
Oh, good.
哦  好
- What? - I just can't believe...
-怎么  -只是不敢相信
...I'm in Rachel Green's room.
我在瑞秋·格林的房间里
What do you mean?
你什么意思
You've been in my room before.
你以前到过我的房间
Yeah, sure, right.
可不是
Like I'd ever be in Rachel Green's room.
就跟我真来过瑞秋·格林房间似的
Okay, I gotta tell you,
好吧  我得跟你说
it's really weird when you use my whole name.
你叫我的全名可真有点儿怪
Sorry.
对不起
- You okay? - Yeah.
-你还好吧  -还行
- Yeah, you had a rough day. - Yeah.
-今天太累了  是吧  -是啊
It's just so weird seeing him like that, you know?
看到他那个样子很奇怪  你知道吗
I mean, he's a doctor.
我是说  他是个医生
You don't expect doctors to get sick.
医生怎么会得病的呢
But we do.
但我们确实会得病
He's gonna be okay, Rach.
他会好的  瑞秋
I don't want him to wake up alone.
我不想让他醒来一个人
I should go to the hospital.
我得去医院
What? No, no. Hey, hey, look.
什么  不  等等  嘿  你看
What?
什么
They gave him a lot of medication.
他服了很多镇静药
He wouldn't even know if you were there.
他甚至都不会知道你在不在那儿
We'll go see him first thing in the morning. Ok?
我们明天一早就去看他  好吗
Really? I shouldn't feel guilty?
真的  我不去也不用于心有愧
No-- God, hey.
不用  天啊  嘿
Rach, you've been an amazing daughter, okay?
瑞秋  你是个好女儿  知道吗
Right now you need to get some rest.
现在  你需要好好休息一下
Okay, maybe you're right.
好吧  也许你说得对
Good night.
晚安
Wait, wait, wait.
等等...
Would you stay here
你能不能在这
with me for a little while?
陪我呆一会儿
- Sure. - Okay.
-当然  -好
Thank you for coming with me today.
谢谢你今天陪我来
Oh, of course.
哦  应该的
Rachel Green is very happy you're in her room.
瑞秋·格林很高兴你在她房间里
Me too. Come here.
我也很高兴  来
I just don't wanna be alone tonight.
我只是不想晚上一个人在这儿
Okay, well,
那好
I can maybe grab a sleeping bag or--
我可以找条睡袋什么的...
No, Rach!
不行  瑞秋
I'm sorry,
抱歉
I just don't think this is a good idea.
我只是觉得这样不好
Well, we won't know that until we do it,
我们不做怎么知道好不好
will we?
对吧
No, look, uh.
不  你看  嗯…
You are upset about your father,
你为你父亲的事儿心烦
and you're feeling vulnerable...
你现在很脆弱
...and I just don't feel it
而且我觉得这时候
would be right.
这么做不对
I feel like I'd be, you know,
我会觉得
taking advantage of you.
这是在占你便宜
What--? Taking advantage?
什么 占便宜
I am giving you the advantage. Enjoy!
我在主动投怀送抱  你尽兴好啦
Look, I'm sure it would be great...
我知道肯定会很美妙...
...but I think one of us has to be thinking clearly.
但我认为我们俩得有一个保持清醒
So I'm gonna go.
所以我要走了
Okay.
好吧
I'll see you in the morning.
明天早上见
I haven't had sex in four months.
我都4个月没有做爱了
I should get a medal for that!
我刚才的高姿态应该得块奖章
Thanks so much for taking me to all those places.
谢谢你们带我去了那么多地方
I had a great time.
我玩得很高兴
I'm glad.
哦  我也很高兴
Listen, I wanna apologize about Chandler, though.
但是  我得为钱德勒道歉
I just did not see this coming.
我没想到他会这样
New York is awesome!
纽约可真棒
What is with you?
你怎么回事儿
You know, I've been to these places before...
你知道吗  我以前去过那些地方
...but I've never really seen them.
但是我都没有好好看过风景
Yeah, you miss a lot when you're mooing.
没错  你学牛叫的时候错过好多风景
Thank you for showing me around.
非常感谢你们带我观光
Oh, it was our pleasure.
哦  我们很高兴陪你去
We're so much enjoying getting to know you.
我们也想跟你熟悉熟悉
Well, if there's anything else you wanna know....
呃  你们还有什么想了解的吗
Okay.
好吧
Can we ask you some questions
你不会介意我问几个
about the father?
有关孩子父亲的问题吧
Oh, sure. Yeah.
哦  没关系
Well, he was my high-school boyfriend,
他是我高中的男朋友
captain of the football team, really cute.
足球队长  很可爱
Got a scholarship and went to college.
后来他得到奖学金  上了大学
That's great.
那不错啊
Yeah, it's almost definitely him.
是啊  差不多就是他了
How's that, now?
那怎么说
Well, there's a chance it's another guy.
也有可能是另外一个人
I mean, I've only ever been with two guys...
我是说  我只跟两个人好过
...but they sort of overlapped.
但是时间上有些重叠
So, what does the other guy do?
那么  另一个人是干什么的
Does he go to college too?
他也上大学了吗
No, he's in prison.
不  他在蹲监狱
Was he falsely accused of something?
那他是被诬告的吧
No.
不
He killed his father with a shovel.
他用铁铲杀了他爸爸
Other than that, he's a great guy.
但是除此之外  他还是个不错的人
I'll bet his dad doesn't think so.
我猜他爸爸不这么想
- Are you awake? - Of course I'm awake.
-你醒着呢吗   -我当然还醒着
Assume from now on that I'm always awake.
从今往后我是睡不着啦
All right, we don't know that it's him.
好啦  我们也不确定就一定是他
I mean, it could be the football guy.
我是说  也可能是那个踢足球的
Honey, it's us.
亲爱的  我们这对儿倒霉蛋
Of course it's the shovel killer.
肯定是摊上那个铁铲杀手
Well, all right, let's say that it is him.
好了  好了  就算是他
Would we not want the baby? No.
我们就不要这孩子了  不
Would we treat him any differently?
我们会对他另眼相待吗
I'd keep an eye on him.
我会一直提防着他的
We have to find out who the father is.
我们一定得查出哪一个是孩子的父亲
- How? - I don't know.
-怎么查  -我不知道
They have tests for these things, right?
这种事儿可以测出来的  对吧
Yes, but maybe we're just overreacting.
是  不过我们也许反应过度了
Easy for you to say.
你说得当然轻巧
He's a father killer.
他杀的是他爸爸
He probably loves his mommy.
他没准儿很爱他老妈
He's probably got a tattoo
他没准儿在挥铲子的胳膊上
that says "Mom" on his shovel-wielding arm.
刺着"妈妈"呢
We'll now count from one to five.
"现在我们从一数到五"
- Good job. - Thank you.
-"说得真好"  -谢谢
- Hey. - Hey, Joey.
-嘿  -嘿  乔伊
Listen, I feel really badly about yesterday,
听我说  昨天的事儿我觉得不太好
and I thought about it a lot.
我想了很多
No, I was too impatient.
我想是我太没有耐心了
So let's try it again.
所以  我们今天再试试
That's okay. I don't need your help.
哦不  不用了  我不用你帮忙了
I worked on it myself,
我可以自学
and I gotta say I am pretty good.
而且我得说我学得还不错嘞
Really, can I hear some of it?
真的  说几句给我听听
Sure, sure.
当然可以
Okay.
好
See?
怎么样
You, you're not--
好吧  你说的不是...
You're not-- You're--
你不是在...
Again, you're not speaking French!
我再次重申  你说的不是法语
Oh, well, I think I am.
哦  我觉着我说的是法语
Yeah, and I think I'm definitely gonna get the part.
而且我肯定能得到那个角色
How could you possibly think that?
你怎么会这么想的
For one thing.
至少
The guy on the tape
磁带上的那家伙说
said I was doing a good job!
我念得不错
Hey, Rach, can you grab me a cup of coffee?
嗨  瑞秋  给我倒杯咖啡好吗
Sure.
当然可以
You've been quiet all morning.
你一早上话不多
Is everything okay?
没事儿吧
- You sure you're all right? - Yep.
-你肯定没事  -当然
Okay.
好
Well, I'm gonna go grab us some breakfast.
好吧  那我去买点早饭
FYI.
有个意见供你参考
There it is.
得  来啦
In the future...
以后
...when a girl asks for some ill-advised sympathy sex,
如果有女孩子需要点不理智的安慰性的爱爱
just do it.
你就满足她好啦
Wait, wait, you're mad at me about last night?
等等  你是因为昨晚的事儿生我的气
I was just trying to do the right thing.
我只是想做对的事
Really?
真的
It seems to me.
对我来说
If you had done the right thing...
要是你做得对的话
...l wouldn't have woken up
我就不会一早醒来
feeling stupid and embarrassed.
感觉又愚蠢又尴尬
I would've woken up feeling comforted and satisfied.
我只会觉得舒适而满意
- Well-- - Oh, stop that!
-呃...  -哦  得了吧
I can't believe this. What you...
我不敢相信  你怎么...
I was just being a good guy.
我只是做了回好人
I treated you with respect and understanding.
我以尊重和同情之心待你
Oh, that is so hot.
啊  那可真性感
Hey, I was looking out for you.
嘿  我是在为你着想
Oh, really? Well, Ross,
哦  真的  罗斯
you know what? I am a big girl.
你要知道  我不是个小丫头
I don't need someone telling me
我不需要有人告诉我
what is best for me.
什么对我来说最好
I gotta say, I've not had sex a lot of times before.
虽说以前我也经常没过成性生活
This is the worst ever!
但这次是最糟糕的
Oh, really? Really?
哦  真的  真的
Well, it wasn't very good for me either.
这对我来说也好不到哪儿去
Okay, you know--?
哦  你猜...
Hey, hey, you know what?
嘿  嘿  你猜怎么着
To avoid this little thing in the future...
为了以后少这种麻烦
...let's just say you and me?
咱们就干脆说定
Never having sex again.
你我以后再也不上床了
What?
什么
That's right! Sex is off the table!
对了  "性"这个字以后免谈
I am never having sex with you again!
我再也不会跟你睡觉啦
Dr. Green, are you feeling better?
格林医生  你感觉好点儿了吗
Hey. How was lunch?
嘿  午饭怎么样
We had a good time.
我们吃得不错
By the way,
对了
I wanted to ask you something.
我想求你一件事
It would really mean a lot to me if the baby was a boy...
这对我来说很重要   如果是个男孩
...that you name him after my father...
你能不能让孩子  随我父亲的名字
...Jiminy Billy Bob.
吉米尼·比利·鲍勃
- Oh, really? - No!
-哦  真的  -不
You were right. That was fun.
你说得没错  这真好玩
I'm gonna go finish packing.
我要去收拾东西了
So is she gonna take the test?
那么  她愿意去做检测吗
No, she doesn't have to.
不  用不着了
I found out who the father is.
我知道谁是父亲
Oh, God.
哦  上帝
It's Shovely Joe, isn't it?
是铁铲乔  对吧
No, it's not.
不  不是的
How do you know?
你怎么知道的
Erica didn't pay attention in sex ed class...
看来艾瑞卡性教育课学得不好
...because the things
她跟蹲监狱的家伙
she did with that prison guy?
做的事
It'd be pretty hard to make a baby that way.
不太可能让她怀孕
Oh, God, what was it?
天呐  什么姿势
The thing we hardly ever do,
是我们很少做的
or the thing we never do?
还是我们从没做过的
The thing we never do.
我们从没做过的
Shovely Joe.
铁铲乔
Whenever you're ready, Joey.
你准备好了就开始吧  乔伊
Right.
好的
I'm sorry, what's going on?
对不起  怎么回事儿
Dude, come on, French it up.
哥们儿  来嘛  说法语啦
Joey, do you speak French?
乔伊  你会说法语吗
You know what? I think this audition is over.
我看这次试镜就到此为止吧
Excuse me?
打扰一下
I am Regine Phalange.
我是瑞金·弗兰基
I was passing by
我刚路过
when I heard this man speaking...
听到这个人在说
...the regional dialect of my French town of Estee Lauder.
我们法国小镇雅诗兰黛的方言
You really think this man is speaking French?
你真的认为这个人在说法语
好的
好的（法语）
我告诉你真相
我告诉你真相（法语）
他是我弟弟
他是我弟弟（法语）
他...
他...（法语）
有点脑残
有点脑残（法语）
你能不能假装夸他一下
你能不能假装夸他一下（法语）
Good job, little buddy.
干得不错  小家伙
That was some really good French.
你的法语讲得很好
But I think we're gonna go with
但是我觉得还是
someone else for the part.
其他人更适合这个角色
All right, but my French was good?
哦  好吧  但是我的法语很好
It was great.
非常好
See?
看到了吧
Emma's down for the night.
艾玛睡着了
Oh, good.
哦  好的
- So I guess I'm gonna take off. - Okay.
-那我看我该走了   -好的
Hey, listen, just before you go--
嘿  听我说  你走之前  我…
I just wanna say thank you
我想再次谢谢你
for coming with me.
能陪我一起去看我爸
Oh, no problem.
没问题
And also, you know, l--
还有  你知道我…
I was thinking about what you said,
我在想你说的话
you know, about the whole sex thing....
你知道的  关于性什么的…
Probably not a great idea to go down that road again.
也许再重蹈覆辙确实不是个好主意
Thank you. I'm glad you agree.
谢谢  我很高兴你也这么想
It's a shame, though.
这也有点可惜
When we did it, it was pretty good.
我是说   我们做的时候感觉不错
Yeah.
对
Yeah, that's true.
对  那倒是真的
Hey, do you remember that one really great time?
嘿  你还记得特别棒的那次
- Oh, yeah! - You know?
-哦  记得  -你记得
It was Valentine's Day.
那天是情人节...
It was your birthday.
是你的生日...
- Oh, yeah. - Oh, yeah.
-哦  对呀  -哦  对呀
Well, I guess that's all in the past now.
我想那都是陈年往事了
- Not even one more time. - Not even once.
-以后再也不干了  -一次也不
No matter how much we want it.
不管我们有多想要
Even if we want it...
即使我们真的...
...really bad.
真的很想要
That's what we decided.
我们就这么说定的
Right.
没错
It's kind of hard, though. You know?
但这有点难哦
Yeah.
是啊
You know. When two people have a connection,
你知道  既然两人有了那种联系
you know, that's--
如果不用...
Just seems like...
就好像
...such a...
好像是
...waste.
种浪费
I hate waste.
我讨厌浪费
- Ross? - Yes?
-罗斯  -嗯
Just so you know...
告诉你...
...with us...
我们之间
...it's never off the table.
那事儿从来也没有免谈一说
Damn it, it's never off the table.
可恶  这还拜托不了了
Okay, can you really tap-dance?
好了  你真的会跳踢踏舞吗
No.
不会
It's off the resume.
从简历上去掉
- Archery? - No.
-箭术  -不会
- Horseback riding? - Would fall off a lot.
-骑马  -经常掉下来
You can drink a gallon of milk in 10 seconds?
你能在十秒钟内喝掉一加仑牛奶
That I can do.
这我能做到
Come on,
得了吧
you can drink a gallon of milk in 10 seconds?
你能在十秒钟内喝掉一加仑牛奶
All right, watch me.
好吧  我喝给你看
Okay, you time me, ready?
你计时  准备好了吗
Ready, go!
预备  开始
You did it!
你成功了